Yingying,
Kak Ying.
you shouldn't have to handle such heavy work, right?
Bagaimana Anda bisa melakukan pekerjaan kasar ini sendiri?
Have a seat.
Cepat duduk, cepat duduk.
Quite right!
Adalah
Have a seat, Yingying.
Kamu cepat duduk Kak Ying.
Have some water.
Minumlah sedikit air.
Have some fruit.
Makan sedikit buah.
What's going on?
Atas dasar apa?
Why am I being replaced?
Kenapa menggantikan posisiku?
I don't care who the new boss is.
Aku tidak peduli siapa presiden baru itu
I won't accept this.
Aku tidak puas.
What's going on?
Kalian ada masalah apa?
It's you.
Ternyata kamu.
It's been a while.
Lama tidak berjumpa.
They say we have a new leader here.
Dengar-dengar pemimpin baru
The beauty of our sales department
Cabang dari penjualan kami
wants to invite you out for dinner.
Ingin mengajakmu makan malam.
What about lunch? We can go together.
Siang nanti, ayo kita bersama.
Zhengzheng,
Positif
guess who I saw today at work?
Coba tebak, hari ini aku melihat siapa di perusahaan?
Your older brother.
Kakakmu
It's been two years
Dua tahun tidak bertemu,
and he seems even more mature.
Dia menjadi dewasa dan stabil lagi.
Is this the surprise you talked about?
Aduh!
What are you doing here?
Kenapa kamu bisa di sini?
What's wrong with your head?
Ada apa dengan kepalamu?
Let me see.
Aku lihat,
I'm done with all the work
Membeli perusahaan
purchasing this company.
Sudah aku urus.
It's just that Dad asked me
Hanya saja Ayah memintaku
to run it personally.
Untuk mengurus sendiri.
Didn't you agree to let me do it?
Bukankah bilang aku yang urus?
I never saw you being so keen
Pertama kali aku melihatmu mengelola perusahaan,
on running a part of the business.
Begitu perhatian.
Could it be
Mungkinkah...
there's another reason?
Ada rahasia apa?
Mr. Wei is really handsome.
Manajer Wei sungguh tidak biasa.
And this restaurant is pretty nice.
Lingkungan restoran ini lumayan bagus.
Miss Wei,
Nona Wei.
to congratulate you on your promotion,
Kita rayakan kenaikan jabatanmu.
let's raise our coffee cups
Menggunakan kopi sebagai pengganti arak
to toast your success.
Bersulang.
Mr. Wei,
Pak Wei.
I happened to be wondering if we could talk about this.
Kebetulan saya ingin berbicara dengan Anda tentang masalah ini.
With my current work experience,
Dengan pencapaianku sekarang,
I am not qualified to be a manager.
Masih tidak bisa menjadi supervisor.
So
Jadi,
I think it would be better
Menurutku,
for me to take my time
Dan membumi
and work my way up slowly.
Satu per satu.
That's fine.
Baiklah.
Let's put business aside.
Tidak membahas bisnis.
Zhengzheng.
Positif
What a coincidence.
Kebetulan sekali.
Take a seat.
Duduklah di sini.
How's your injury?
Apakah lukamu sudah membaik?
I'm fine.
Aku baik-baik saja.
Why didn't you
Keluar makan.
ask me out to this meal?
Kenapa tidak mengajakku keluar?
I'd like to touch up my makeup.
Aku ingin berdandan.
Mr. Wei,
Pak Wei.
where is the bathroom?
Di mana toiletnya?
Just down the hall.
Di belakang
I still don't know where.
Dia tidak kenal.
Why don't you show me the way?
Bawa dia pergi.
Do you remember this place?
Masih ingat tempat ini?
Wow.
Wah!
It's still the same.
Semuanya benar-benar sama.
Tomorrow.
Besok.
Tomorrow I'll officially confess my love to you.
Besok aku akan menyatakan cintaku padamu.
I won't be your little brother anymore.
Berhenti menjadi adikmu.
I want to be your official boyfriend.
Aku ingin resmi menjadi pacarmu.
(Next episode) I'm not a kid anymore.
Aku bukan anak kecil lagi.
Alright.
Baik
You're not a kid anymore.
Kamu bukan anak kecil lagi.
Then,
Kalau begitu
let's do something
Mari kita lakukan sedikit.
that adults do.
Yang seharusnya Tuan lakukan
- You...
Kau...
What are you doing here?
Kenapa kamu ada di sini?